And here we have it.
여기 있네요
The user interface is completed.
사용자 인터페이스가 완성됐어요
The extra notification came through on my phone and my watch, and you can see the wonderful trace of
제 폰과 시계에 추가 알림이 떴어요 여기서 무슨 일이 있었는지 멋진
what went on here with the surfaced conclusion at the bottom.
흔적을 볼 수 있죠 아래에 드러난 결론도요
And it's actually just you just saw it up in the memory and it's just going off right now because it's
방금 메모리에서 보셨는데 지금 작동되고 있어요 우리가 말하는 동안
kicking off another run while we speak.
다른 런이 시작됐거든요
Uh, I left it too long, but there you got the idea.
너무 오래 놔뒀네요 대충 아시겠죠?
It ran, it completed, we saw the latest memories, and it was able to show the trace of the thinking
실행되고 완성되며 가장 최근의 기억을 봤죠 자신이 한 생각과 일어난 일을 흔적으로
that it was doing and what was happening.
남겼어요
And it will be repeating this every five minutes.
5분마다 반복될 거예요
I should probably slow that down a bit.
비트 속도를 늦춰야겠어요
And notifying me all through the day and night of new deals.
밤낮으로 새로운 거래에 대해 알려줬고요
So hopefully this has been, uh, satisfying for you to see it come together.
완성된 모습을 보니 만족스러우셨길 바라요
Hopefully you're running this yourself and seeing the same thing, seeing the conversation between the
여러분이 직접 실행해 같은 걸 보셨길 바랍니다 에이전트 프레임워크에서
different agents in our agent framework and seeing this being surfaced and highlighted in this user
다른 에이전트 간의 대화를 보고 이 사용자 인터페이스에서 강조되어 드러나는
interface, and seeing how easy, of course, how incredibly easy it is to use Gradio to build something
걸 보고 얼마나 쉬운지, 물론 Gadio를 이용해 규격화된 뭔가를 구축하는 게 얼마나 쉬운지
off the shelf that is able to give us such great insights into what's going on and give us so much functionality,
보셨길 바랍니다 무슨 일이 벌어지고 있는지에 대한 훌륭한 통찰력을 주고 화면 모음에 많은 기능성을
all in a set of screens.
제공하죠
So with this, I hope that you enjoy working with this agent framework.
에이전트 프레임워크와 즐겁게 작업하시길 바라요
Make it your own.
당신 것으로 만들어요
I will probably go and fix the fact that the screen should refresh whilst it's also processing, so
프로세싱 중에도 스크린이 새로 고침돼야 한다는 사실을 수정할 겁니다 그러니 기다릴
you don't have to to wait.
필요 없어요
But if I don't do it, then by all means you should do it yourself and add on more to this user interface
하지만 제가 안 하면 여러분이 직접 하셔야 해요 이 사용자 인터페이스에 추가해 여러분만의
and make this your own.
것으로 만들어야죠
Not only have you hopefully trained your own LLM to be even more accurate than R1, but also you're
여러분 자신의 LLM이 R1보다 더 정확하도록 훈련했을 뿐 아니라 더 많은 기능성을
adding more functionality, improving the prompts, and finding other ways that we can bring this to
추가하고 프롬프트 성능을 향상하고 이것을 활성화하고 UI
life and also add add more features and surface them in the UI.
표면에 더 많은 기능을 추가할 방법을 찾고 있죠
And then when you've done that, push your code so that I can see it and admire it, and other students
제가 보고 감탄할 수 있도록 코드를 푸시하세요 다른 학생들이 여러분이
can take advantage of the changes that you've made.
바꾼 걸 이용할 수 있도록요
Enjoy working with this agent framework, and I will see you for the next video where we wrap things
에이전트 프레임워크와 즐겁게 작업하세요 다음 비디오에서 마무리할 때
up.
뵙죠